So let's go ahead and let's create a new folder.
让我们继续，来创建一个新的文件夹
So we're gonna do MK dir, hardhat, smart contract lottery, FCC
`mkdir hardhat-smartcontract-lottery-fcc`
or smart contract, raffle, whatever you want to call it,
或者叫 `smartcontract-raffle`，随你的便了
then we're going to cd into our hard hat, smart contract lottery Free Code Camp.
接着，我们 `cd` 进入到我们的 `hardhat-smartcontract-lottery-fcc`
And we're going to type code period,
然后输入 `code .`
or we're going to open this up in a new folder, however we choose to do.
或者我们也可以在一个新的文件夹中打开它，看你的选择了
So now that we're in our new folder,
现在我们已经有了一个新的文件夹
we're going to create our new hard hat project.
可以开始创建我们新的 Hardhat 项目了
So we're going to do yarn, add dash dash dev hard hat.
我们来执行 `yarn add --dev hardhat`
And we'll get our node modules are package dot JSON and our yarn dot lock.
我们获得了 "node_modules", "package.json" 以及 "yarn.lock"
Now we'll do yarn hardhat. To get started with a new project,
现在我们运行 `yarn hardhat`，开启一个新的项目
and we're just going to select create an empty hard hat dot config dot j s
我们直接选择“创建一个空的 hardhat.config.js”
("Create an empty hardhat.config.js")
because we know what a basic project looks like.
因为我们知道一个基本的项目是什么样子的
And we're gonna give this project the customizations that we want to see,
并且我们要对这个项目做一些我们想要的自定义配置
we're going to create an empty hard hat dot config.
我们将创建一个空的 "hardhat.config"
And now in here we have a blank hardhead.config.js with almost nothing in here.
现在，我们就有了这个空白的 "hardhat.config.js"，这里几乎没有任何内容
So we're starting completely from scratch.
我们几乎是完全的从头开始
Now we're going to add all of our dependencies in here.
现在我们就要在这里添加我们所有的依赖项了
And oftentimes, you'll add these sequentially as you build
通常，你会按照顺序来添加它们
but we're just going to add them all in one line,
但我们打算直接一行就把它们全部都添加了
and there are a lot of them. So we've left a copy, paste the whole section of the full blockchain solidity course, J S,
它们真的太多了，所以我们在 "full-blockchain-solidity-course-js" 中留下了一个可供复制粘贴的部分
for you to just copy, paste, so you can install everything in one go.
这样你就可以直接复制粘贴，一次性安装所有内容了
So grab that line, and it's going to have everything that we've been talking about.
获取这一行，它包含了我们要讨论的所有内容
And we'll just hit enter, and we'll install all of these.
我们只要按下 Enter，就会安装所有的这些东西了
And as you create more and more projects,
随着你创建的项目越来越多
you'll get the feel of what you like for your dependencies
你会感知到哪些依赖库是你喜欢的
and what tools that you like to use.
以及哪些工具是你爱用的
Remember, at the end of the day,
记住，每当一天的工作结束时
the tool that's best for you and best for the job is the tool that you like the most.
对你和你的工作而言，最好的工具就是你最喜欢的工具
There never really is a one tool fits all,
从来没有一种工具可以应对所有的情形
there's almost always going to be trade offs.
几乎总是会有取舍
Alright, now that we have all those dependencies installed,
好了，现在我们已经安装好了全部依赖
if we look at our package, JSON will have this massive dev dependencies,
如果我们看一下 "package.json"，里面会有这么一大堆依赖库
we'll have everything in Node modules will have everything in yarn dot lock.
我们所需的所有东西都已经在 "node_modules" 和 "yarn.lock" 里了
And of course, as we know, in order for any of these to actually work,
当然了，我们都知道，要想让它们都能生效
we need to add them into our Hardhead config.
还需要把它们都添加进我们的 "hardhat.config" 中
Now, there's a lot of stuff to add in here as well.
现在，还有一堆东西也需要添加
So like once again, if you want to come to the heart at smart contract, lottery, FCC,
所以再一次，如果你愿意的话，可以来到 "hardhat-smartcontract-lottery-fcc" 这里
and go to the Hardhead config,
打开 "hardhat.config"
you can just copy paste everything and place it into your project
你可以直接复制粘贴这里的所有内容到你的项目中去
so that you don't have to always type everything out yourself.
这样你就不用总是亲自输入这些内容了
Meclabs Hardhead waffle anomic labs started ether scan harder to deploy
"nomiclabs/hardhat-waffle", "nomiclabs/hardhat-etherscan", "hardhat-deploy"
slitted coverage, or had gas reporter heart had contract sizer,
"solidity-coverage", "hardhat-gas-reporter", "hardhat-contract-sizer"
which we haven't talked about yet. But we will Don't worry.
有些我们还没有谈到过，但不用担心，之后会的
And then require dot env dot config.
最后是 `require("dotenv").config()`
And as you all know, all these little semicolons are popping up
还有，你是知道的，这些分号又出现了
and those are going to drive me absolutely crazy.
它们会让我疯掉的
So once again, we can create a dot prettier, RC.
所以再一次，我们创建一个 ".prettierrc"
And if you want to copy this as well,
如果你愿意的话，这个也可以复制
from one of your previous projects are free to do so.
就是从你之前的项目里，请自便吧
One thing that I added in here was a print width of 100.
这里要额外添加一项的内容是 `"printWidth": 100`
This just changes how long a line can be before it goes on to a new line.
它只是改变了一行文字可以有多长，超过该长度将换行显示
That's the only difference here.
这就是唯一的区别
Now if we go to our config and hit save, they go away, thank goodness.
现在我们前往 "config" 然后点击保存，哈，它们不见了，真是谢天谢地
Now if we look at our solidity version,
现在我们再来看一下我们的 solidity 版本
we're currently using zero point 7.3.
目前我们使用的是 "0.7.3"
Let's go ahead and update that to 8.8 or 8.7, or whatever you want to use.
我们来把它更新到 "8.8" 或是 "8.7"，你想用哪个都行
Now that we have all the basic setup, we can begin coding our smart contracts.
现在我们已经完成了所有的基本设置，可以开始编写智能合约了